Sonic the Hedgehog was so excited today
was his birthday and his lover
Bartleby Montclair of Dresden has agreed
to take him on a picnic to the park to
celebrate Sonic waited patiently for his
lover
Bartleby to get there to pick him up
eventually
the biggest limo of Sonic has ever seen
had pulled up into his driveway
the limo driver casually got out of the
limo and bowed to Sonic before making
his way to one of the car doors he
opened the door and inside was that the
most beautiful man Sonic has ever laid
his eyes on it was his lover Barnaby
butt naked with nothing but a picnic
basket covering his crotch Sonic could
almost feel a nosebleed coming on so he
quickly covered his nose Bartleby
giggled at this cute little display and
and told Sonic to get in the limo with
him Sonic climbed in next to Bartleby
and hugged him the limo driver then shut
the door went back to the front and sat
back down behind the wheel and soon they
were off again since Bartleby had so
much money he was able to buy the
fastest limo on earth they drove all the
way to the other side of town in less
than five seconds and stopped at a local
park the two lovers Bartleby and Sonic
climbed out of the limo and scanned the
area looking for the perfect spot for
their picnic Bartleby looked down at his
Sonic and asked him where he would like
to sit Sonic blushed and point under a
nearby tree it was perfect
Bernal B thought Bartleby picked up his
and carried him over to the tree
where he proceeded to drop him back to
the ground Sonic fell to the ground
headfirst his stomach hitting the ground
Bartleby gave him a good slap on the ass
before pulling out a picnic blanket and
setting it on the ground the blue
Hedgehog could feel his mouth filling up
with drool he wasn't sure if it was
because of all the food or because of
Bartleby's big bulging muscles and plump
ass but dear God did he want a taste
it was at this point that Bartleby
noticed Sonic staring at him he flexed
his muscles just a tiny bit and gave
Sonic a nosebleed
suddenly almost in an instant the entire
sky turned dark gray Sonic who is afraid
of water quickly ran over to Bartleby
side and hugged him
Bartleby looked down at his bitching saw
tears streaming down his face Sonic
hates the rain and Bartleby knows this
he wiped the tears from his bitch's face
and smiled Sonic looked up into
Bartleby's eyes and knew that there was
nothing to be afraid of as long as he
was with his lover
Bartleby Montclair of Dresden the two of
them leaned in and kissed each other on
the lips suddenly it started to rain but
strangly enough neither of them cared
Bartleby's Butler walked over with a big
umbrella and handed it to the lovers
they continued the picnic as planned and
ate their food before eventually having
hot and sweaty sex the end